Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
The Lion’s Dream
In the previous episode, after the little goats defeated Team Rats,
Blazey continues to drill the fundamentals as always.
Sparky wants to learn cooler basketball skills.
So he trained alone, but unexpectedly ran into the popular idol Lion Jay.
Sparky was completely impressed by Lion Jay.
Little did he know, Lion Jay would be their next opponent.
Sparky, hold up!
We already finished our 100 laps, Sparky!
I’m off!
He leaves right after practice these past few days. I don’t know what he’s up to.
I don’t care what he’s doing.
I don’t want to do anything anymore. I just want to rest.
Kids,
your task tomorrow is to scout Team Lion Heart’s training session.
Know your enemy, know yourself.
No training tomorrow!
Let’s begin.
Well…
What’s up?
I’m just curious why you’re willing to teach me.
Everyone else looks down on us Goat Clan, thinking we’re too weak.
I admire anyone who genuinely loves basketball.
Thank you.
So, will you teach me how to dunk today?
No, you’re learning how to post up.
But I don’t want to learn that.
I want to learn how to dunk!
Look at your height and build. Playing in the post is exactly what you need right now.
Master the fundamentals first.
You have to learn to walk before you can run.
How come you sound just like my coach?
Come on.
Try to stop me.
Steal the ball.
You need to use your body to seal off and pressure the defender.
While you’re applying force, you must keep your center of gravity stable.
Once you’ve backed down your defender and generated enough space,
you can choose your go-to move to finish.
That’s how you post up.
My turn!
Lion Jay!
—Lion Jay!　—So many people.
—Lion Jay!　—Stay close to me, don’t get separated!
It would be great if Sparky came too.
He’s strong, so he could squeeze a path for me.
—Lion Jay!　—Sparky has been acting all mysterious lately.
I don’t know what he’s doing.
Lion Jay!
Jonie, wait a minute.
Don’t push!
Lion Jay!
I’m so dizzy.
Paddi, are you alright?
The fans are so passionate!
Let’s get one last photo.
Alright, alright.
This wraps up today’s fan meeting.
Please exit in an orderly fashion.
Yes, thank you everyone for coming out to see me.
See you next time.
Wait, we’re not fans.
We are Team Defenders, your next opponent.
Whatever.
Let’s go, Lion Jay.
The Grassland’s best-selling magazine wants to interview you.
Where’s Lion Jay? Why has he gone missing again?
Hurry up and find him for me.
Yes, sir.
Try to dunk again.
Sparky, are you alright?
It hurts.
Didn’t I tell you to master the fundamentals first?
Forcing a dunk like that easily leads to injury.
Alright.
You look exhausted.
I’ve had way too much on my plate these past few days.
And I went to practice at night, so I’ve got these bags under my eyes.
If you don’t want to do those events, you can just tell your agent.
Why do you have to listen to him?
Because my agent is my benefactor.
One day, we will play basketball on a bigger stage.
That was amazing! You’re a born star!
Who are you?
I’m a basketball idol agent. Do you want to play real basketball?
I’ve been scouting you guys for a long time.
Your basketball skills are absolutely beautiful.
I can get you onto a pro court and make you a basketball idol.
Can I really?
Of course.
Lion Jay!
Please take a look!
Get ready to style!
If this keeps up, we’re gonna lose.
Image comes first, winning comes second!
You guys should feed the ball to Lion Jay more. Make sure he gets to dunk and score.
I thought being an idol would be easier.
Why don’t you just leave the agent and quit the idol life?
He’s the one who gave me the chance to play on a real court.
I don’t want to be ungrateful.
Alright, we’ll do as you say.
Sometime later…
I heard you’re nice with it. Let’s have a game!
You check up.
Turns out you’re all hype and no skill. You fold so easily.
You don’t deserve to be on the court at all.
It’s fine, as long as you have a good image.
Give me another cool pose.
Nice.
One day, I’ll prove my game isn’t just all hype.
I am qualified to stand on the court.
So you see, looking cool isn’t what matters on the court.
Fundamentals are everything.
As long as you put in the work, dunking will be a piece of cake.
Really?
Come on, today I’ll teach you the most critical skill for a power forward.
The most critical skill?
That’s right.
It’s about grabbing rebounds.
Rebounds?
The key to rebounding
is anticipating where the ball will land after bouncing off the rim,
and getting a step ahead of everyone else.
That way, you get inside position to grab the board,
clean up missed shots,
and create second-chance opportunities for your teammates.
That is rebounding.
The one who controls the rebound dominates the game.
Really?
Of course.
Let’s get to it! Basketball is so much fun!
Sparky has been disappearing lately. What has he been up to?
Lion Jay!
Where are you, Lion Jay?
Lion Jay is just like Sparky,
always slipping away by himself?
Lion Jay!
I finally found you!
Hurry up, the Grassland’s best-selling magazine wants to interview you!
Hold on.
At this rate, Lion Jay won’t even have time to practice basketball.
It’s you goat again.
If you’re a scrub, don’t drag others down with you.
If you want to practice, go work out on your own.
Let’s move.
Lion Jay, say something!
Sorry, I’ll head back with you.
Don’t hang out with these weaklings anymore.
If reporters photograph you, it will ruin your image.
We, the Goat Clan, are not weak at all! I challenge you to a game!
Challenge?
If we win the next game,
you have to let Lion Jay play real basketball
and stop forcing him to be an idol.
Boring.
We will definitely win.
When did you guys get here?
We’ve been here. We heard everything.
Don’t look down on us.
Don’t cregret it when you lose.
Winning or losing doesn’t matter. Let’s go.
To be continued…